# **Hejun Wang**

GitHub | Email: hejun\_wang@zju.edu.cn | Mobile: 17789791146

## **BIOGRAPHY**

I am a highly experienced **Deep Learning** investigator with over **1** years of experience in **Autonomous Vehicle** and have an EI paper with me as the first author. I have rich knowledge of popular frameworks such as **Pytorch, Tensorflow**. Furthermore, I am a skilled **Embedded System** engineers. **Embodied AI** that senses from **real world**, thinks in **real-time** and actuates upon **real things** always interests me.

### **AWARDS**

- · Third Class Scholarship of Zhejiang University
- 2022 Third Prize for National Mathematical Modelling Competition

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Zhejiang University, Chu Kochen Honors College**

Undergraduate of Cyber-system and Control

Hangzhou, Zhejiang, China Sep 2020 – Present

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Quamtun Computing Researcher**

Supervisor: Xi Wan, Email: xinwan@zju.edu.cn

Feb 2022 – Jun 2022 Zhejiang University, Hangzhou, Zhejiang, China

- Simulate the application of Shor code in **Quantum-Bits Transformation**.
- · Based on the Toric Code, an algorithm is designed to correlate random errors in quantum computing.
- · Design an effective scheme to reduce the error rate of quantum computing.

## **Provincial Innovation Programme of Zhejiang Province**

Mar 2022 - Jun 2023

Supervisor: Xiong Rong, Email: <a href="mailto:rxiong@zju.edu.cn">rxiong@zju.edu.cn</a>

Zhejiang University, Hangzhou, Zhejiang, China

- Put forward a novel representation for continuous trajectory of Fourier Series.
- Propose an effective and efficient hierarchy of end-to-end autonomous vehicles.
- Achieve **state-of-the-art performances** both in simulations and real world.

# Oral Presentation for IEEE Conference of Real-time Computing and Robot 2023

Jul 2023

Supervisor: Xiong Rong, Email: rxiong@zju.edu.cn

Datong, Shanxi, China

- Introduce Knowledge Distillation for human-like semantic reasoning.
- First Author of Knowledge Distillation On Driving Intention Generator:Learn Human-like Reasoning.
- Give an oral presentation on RCAR.